We're actually partnering with IBM to build
我们与 IBM 合作创建了这个精彩的项目
this really great project for everyone to sort of utilize in the classroom.
让学员可以学以致用
Can you give us a little insight into the platform that they'll
你能简要介绍下学员将使用的平台
be using and sort of the data that they'll be getting out of it?
以及将要处理的数据吗？
Right. Yeah, so the project is cool.
好的这个项目很酷
I like the project,
我很喜欢这个项目
I thought it was a great idea when we got started working on it. So what is the project?
我们最初开始创建这个项目的时候 我就觉得这个想法特别棒那么到底是什么项目呢
Well on Watson studio,
在 Watson 工作室
an important component as we discussed was is the community and
有一个很重要的平台是社区
the community is this collaborative ecosystem of a curated datasets,
该社区是一个协作生态系统
articles, notebooks or other kinds
里面精选了一些数据集、文章、notebook
of assets that are out there in the world of data science,
以及数据科学、机器学习
machine learning and artificial intelligence.
和人工智能领域将会用到的各种其他资源
Our users on the platform interact with these assets.
平台用户将会与这些资源互动
So what the students are building and what we've built is
学员将针对社区中的这些资源
a recommendation system for these assets in the community.
构建一个推荐系统 我们也创建了这样的系统
So one thing is that what we do is we go out there ourselves
IBM 团队也创建了一些模型
and we curate also with models that we developed here at IBM,
并使用这些模型
all this kind of all these assets that are out there.
对社区中的各种资源进行筛选
What the students will be doing is building in that part where it makes it personal for
学员将创建一个网络应用
an individual user and providing
该应用能够向用户
that personalized recommendation experience with a web app.
推荐个性化的资源
Cool. So it sounds like this is actually something that isn't
好的听起来 你们平台还没有这样的系统
on your platform but could be really useful to people on your plan.
但是这样的系统对于平台用户来说很有用
Yeah, that's right.
是的
Now that's very cool. So, students will be working on a recommendation system to
太酷了所以 学员将创建一个推荐系统
sort of like personalize recommendations for people who are already in the community?
向社区中的已有用户推荐个性化的资源？
That's right. Yes, so the data that they'll have is anonymized data of
是的学员将用到的数据是匿名数据
the interactions between all of the different kinds of articles and
包含了我们的用户与社区中的
datasets and that sort of thing we have in the community and our users.
各种文章 数据集等资源的互动操作
So there's that communication between what they're actually doing on the platform,
这些数据包括
interacting with those assets,
用户与这些资源的实际互动操作
and all of that is actually part of the data that they'll take advantage of.
学员将利用这些互动数据
So that's pretty exciting I think.
这很让人兴奋
Yeah, it sounds like a really cool project.
听起来是个很酷的项目
It also sounds like so students will be able to sort of tackle
学员可以从多个角度
this recommendation system however they might want
创建这样的推荐系统
to which could be like looking at how users are connected,
例如观察用户之间有何关系
how articles are connected,
文章之间有何关系
how different types of medium are connected,
不同媒介之间有何关系
and there's like lots of different ways that they could go about creating a solution.
创建方法有很多种
Yeah.
是的
Very cool.
好酷